Hey, boy.
Boy.
Where'd you come from?
Blaise!
There you are. Come on.
Hi there.
Hi.
Thanks for finding him.
Yeah, no. He kinda found me.
We just moved in.
Right back there.
Welcome.
Is that yours?
Yeah.
Yeah, that's mine.
I suppose that makes us neighbors.
Alright, well. We oughta head home.
Come on, Blaise.
Hey, I'm... I'm Jonas.
Ford.
I'm Casey Caraway.
Where'd you go?
Found a buzztail in the barn.
Just walked out to the woods a bit.
I'll deal with this.
The check valve on the hose is leakin'.
We'll need to use
the kitchen pipes for today.
- Mom's not gonna like that.
- Yeah, let's see how she likes it...
...when we can't afford her rum and smokes
'cause we're too backed up. Hey.
You remember how I showed you. Shut off
that water supply and let the pressure out.
And Jonas...
...when that snake finds its way back...
...you kill it.
Hey, boy.
- Mornin'.
- Morning.
- Sleep okay?
- Yeah.
- That coffee I'm smelling?
- Yep.
Got some toast too.
There's nothin' to put on it though.
I'll leave you some cash.
Why don't you go into town today and
pick us up a few things. How's that sound?
Sure.
Here.
You out did yourself, baby girl.
Are you nervous?
Nervous about what?
New... new station, new town.
Catching bad guys is your daddy's trade.
He can take it anywhere.
Why? Do I look nervous?
Come here.
Come on.
Let me have your hand.
You feel it?
Can't get any calmer than that.
Casey.
I'm sorry we had to move.
I'm proud of ya for making the best of it.
I'll get us out of here as quick as I can.
Before you know it.
Blaise, come here.
Hi, ma'am.
My name's Casey Caraway.
My daddy and I...
...we just moved into the house
down the road.
I met your son Jonas this morning.
- Is he home by any chance?
- What's your business with him?
No business. I was just about
to head into town...
No, no, no, Jonas, he don't go to town.
So he can't show you nothin'
that you wouldn't see for yourself.
No...
...I guess I just mean the way
to get to know him a little...
Hey, cowboy. I was lookin' for you.
I know.
Your mom...
Yeah, she...
...she gets... sad sometimes.
You gonna be in trouble?
I don't care.
Where you goin'?
Nowhere really.
Do you wanna come?
Yeah.
Blaise, come on.
Come on.
So how's the school here?
I start on Monday.
Oh, it's good. But I don't really go anymore.
- Really?
- Yeah.
And your parents are okay with that?
I hope so, it was their idea.
And here I thought I'd have
someone to cheat off of.
Probably doing you a favor in that case.
And your family?
- Why'd y'all move here?
- Actually my daddy grew up...
...the next county over.
He says they need a lot eyes
and ears because all of the...
...dirty trading coming through town.
And your ma?
She okay with the move?
My mom's dead.
When I was a baby. Cancer.
Sorry.
Can't miss what you never had.
That smell alright to you?
Yeah.
There you are, baby girl.
Was beginning to worry about you a bit.
Hi, Daddy. This is our neighbor Jonas.
Mr. Caraway.
So that's your old ranch
down the road, is it?
Yes, sir.
Not many ranchers around here
still see worth it to stick it out.
Something to admire there.
Can't be easy living.
Nah. It ain't so bad, sir.
I hope you're hungry.
Got some steaks.
That-a-girl. Let me take that bag off ya.
I'll go 'round back, fire up the grill.
I take it your momma's got a nice dinner
waiting for you, that right?
Yes, sir.
Call me Wayne.
Casey, you come in soon now.
Come on, Blaise.
Well, thanks for showing me around.
Yeah.
Sorry if I might've spoiled
any other things...
Nah, you... you didn't spoil nothin'.
Good.
Hey, where the hell you been?
Just showing Casey around town,
being friendly.
That's what neighbors oughta be, don't they?
You tuck in that lip. And you are not to
just run on out of here without notice.
I wouldn't have had to if Ma
didn't slam the door on her face.
Hey, you left me high and dry today, son.
I fell behind a great deal
cause of your selfishness.
Pa. I ain't selfish, okay? I work
just as hard as any ranch hand...
...that gets paid and I don't
complain or ask for nothing.
I'm sorry for runnin' out on you.
I'm gonna finish chopping the wood
I rounded up this morning...
...then reinforce the pen
all like I was supposed to.
Jonas?
Forget the pen.
- It'll be there tomorrow.
- I know. But I got plans tomorrow.
Do you know people can see
for three miles on flat land?
That's pretty far.
It's not far enough.
It's always been my dream
to see the ocean one day.
My mom used to say
how beautiful the coast is.
Said she felt trapped by the land.
Told me the ocean is freedom.
Thought you said your mom died
when you were a baby.
That was a lie.
Why?
I guess it...
...just hurts too much to remember her.
You...
...you lie a lot?
All the time.
You don't think about...
God or...
I think God's also a lie.
It's just something someone made up
to keep people from being bad.
Like Santa Claus for grown ups.
But I don't need to lie with you...
...not anymore.
Ask me anything and I'll tell you the truth.
Well...
...you wanna be my girlfriend?
Yeah.
Hey... I got you somethin'.
There's two of them,
the other one's back at my house.
Now if we need to talk to each other, we can.
I love it.
Good.
- So I was thinking maybe tomorrow...
- She's busy.
Why are you hidin', Daddy?
- I ain't hidin', I'm waitin'.
- It's my fault she's late, sir, I took us...
Head on home.
It's my time with my daughter now.
- I guess I'll come by tomorrow, probably...
- You got shit in your ears, boy?
Come on, Blaise.
Wanted to celebrate
with my baby girl tonight.
I made spaghetti Bolognese. Your favorite.
I'm not hungry.
Good thing I tossed it then.
I wouldn't get too attached to that boy.
Looks like we're getting out of this
shit hole sooner than I thought.
That's too bad.
'Cause I was starting to like it here.
Stop.
Come down.
You look like her.
You talk like her.
Look at me.
Don't be like her.
You're my blood. You're a Caraway.
It's you and me, Casey.
Say it.
It's you and me.
Wait.
I said wait, goddammit!
Come on, boy. You wanna
fuck around with my daughter?
You wanna do that?
Hell, yeah! You ever bob for apples?
Oh, hell yeah!
Daddy!
Daddy, stop it! Daddy, stop it, please!
- Back up!
- Stop!
Daddy, stop!
- Daddy, stop!
- You see?
- Daddy, please stop it, that's enough now!
- You're alright, boy.
Daddy, that's enough now!
- Big breath, now.
- No, Dad! No! Please stop it!
It's you and me, Dad!
It's you and me! Please, stop it!
Dad, please!
Next time I see you 'round my house...
...'round my daughter...
...I'll hold you under for good.
Casey, get in the house!
I said, get in the house!
Jonas? Jonas, are you there?
- Yeah, I'm here.
- You okay?
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm fine. You?
I'm so sorry.
You didn't do nothin'.
You shouldn't be there with him.
It ain't right.
No, Jonas, you don't understand.
My dad...
I ain't afraid of him.
You should be.
Didn't see you in there today, Mr. Ford.
Quite a sermon you missed.
I need to talk to you
'bout one of your officers, sir.
- Mr. Caraway.
- Well, go on then.
He's no good, sir.
Gonna need more than that.
No good, how?
It's how he treats his daughter.
I understand you two have become
pretty close, am I correct?
Yes, sir.
And this complaint of yours
wouldn't have anything to do...
...with a potential complaint of his about
you spending all day with her, would it?
- No.
- But he has made such an objection?
I saw him beat her.
And he went on afterward
to drown me half to death.
Well, that doesn't sound quite right.
But what puzzles me about this, you see...
...is that kids are a product
of their parents.
Now Casey's bout the sweetest,
happiest little girl...
...these old eyes ever seen.
And considerin' her momma
ain't been around for some time...
...I credit Sergeant Caraway with
the type of young lady she's become.
Now, regardin' all this hitting
and drowning, I'll surely look into it...
...'cause that's my job,
but I will tell you this...
...you ain't Casey's family.
You might share spit and secrets,
but the two of you's don't share blood.
And the only business you have with her,
is what her father says so.
You go on now.
Well, hell, boy.
I was on the fence 'bout you,
but it's official now.
I like you.
Got a pretty good pair...
...considerin' they ain't dropped yet.
Course that being said...
...get off my property.
You ain't welcome.
- You're a bad man.
- Is that so?
And what's your idea
of a good man, your daddy?
Some hard bum who keeps his family
locked up on his ranch like it's a damn tomb.
He don't beat on us.
Never laid a finger.
That's cause he's a coward.
You don't know nothin' about him.
That's where you're wrong, son.
You see... there's only
two kinds of men in this world...
...your daddy and me.
Now, way I see it, you've got two options...
...and I'm sorry to say not either of 'em...
...involves you having a friendship
with my baby girl.
Option number one...
...we be civil, as all neighbors oughta be.
We see each other in town...
...we nod, smile, be on our respective ways.
Option number two...
...I make life for your family a living hell.
One little phone call
'bout violated regulations...
...and I'll have land inspectors
so far up your daddy's ass...
...the cattle will be impressed
how hard he shits.
You keep coming around here,
doing what you do...
...and I'll know which option
you've chosen for yourself.
And your family.
Pa.
Yeah.
Don't shush me.
Damn it, Elbert,
I'm right in the middle of this thing.
- You're always right in the middle...
- Pa.
What?
Can I talk to you?
Porch.
Well?
It's Mr. Caraway, sir.
Casey's daddy.
What about him?
I saw him hit Casey.
And when I tried to protect her...
...he dragged me outside
and held my head in a basin.
What do you mean...
...when you tried to protect her?
I ran inside and I... tried to protect her.
Well, that was a pretty damn
foolish thing to do now, wasn't it?
What the hell was I supposed to do, Pa?
Just watch him beat on her?
Now it probably wasn't like that.
He's a man of the law.
I ain't sayin' that makes him a saint,
I'm sayin' it ain't up to us to judge.
You need to be smart in this life, son.
Think before you act.
You don't go running into a man's house
uninvited and start attacking him.
And a police officer no less.
You have any idea the reign of shit...
- ...that man can bring down on this family!
- She needs help, Pa.
- Gotta do something.
- Like what?
Run over there throwin' punches?
The only thing that'll do is wind me up
in the drunk tank with a court date.
You are a coward.
Yeah.
You know, you and your momma...
...oughta take a little trip sometime.
'Cause this world will eat you up whole.
And I'll tell you something else...
...you ever talk to me like this...
Casey?
Casey, you there?
Casey, are you there?
Casey?
I know damn well you're awake.
Dipshit!
I'll tell you what. You sit
your bag down in between us...
...and I'll throw mine over.
Fuck!
Something was taken
out of my truck while I was here.
This was the only place
it could've been taken. Speak!
- There was a boy.
- A boy?
I saw a boy. He was hiding outside before.
He had a... he had a bag with him.
Casey!
Casey! Come back!
What's in the bag?
You took this from my dad?
Who'd he take it from?
I don't know. But he killed 'em for it.
- What were you thinking?
- That home ain't safe for you.
We had to get you out of there.
And now 'cause of this money we can.
Where are we gonna go?
Jonas, you there?
You can still get out of this, son.
I'll make a deal with you.
Bring my daughter and my bag
and that'll be the end of it.
No harm, no foul.
But, Jonas...
...if you don't return what's mine...
...if you make me chase you...
...it's gonna get mean...
...and you're gonna wish I drowned your ass.
Fuck!
Jonas?
Yeah.
You praying?
No.
Now might be a good time.
Come on, Jonas, hurry up.
Come on.
Let's go, Jonas.
Go, go, go, go.
Blaise. Blaise, come here.
Sunday school.
The best place to be, every Sunday morning.
Alright.
I lost count twice, but...
...I think I got around
four hundred and thirty thousand.
I've got about five hundred
and fifty thousand.
So that's nine hundred and eighty total.
That's almost a million dollars.
- Do you know what that means?
- Means we're rich.
No, Jonas. This is not our money.
Hey, well, it ain't your pa's neither.
I stole from him
just like he stole from them...
...so we got as much right to it as he does.
We deserve it...
...'cause we're good.
It's only half.
And it's just a back up.
So, if we ever need more money,
we'll come back and dig it up.
So where do you wanna go?
The ocean.
Help you with something?
I want a gun.
And I wanna retire.
Not old enough.
Maybe I can help with that.
Where'd you get that?
Does it matter?
Single action Colt. Thirty-eight.
It's an antique.
What's wrong with those?
These are on the books.
It's this one or nothing.
- Does it work?
- It works.
I'll take it then. Some bullets too.
The hell you want with this anyway?
Protect my family.
All of it.
You get the other half
when you show me how to use it.
Won't be much longer.
It doesn't hurt now, Jonas.
Stop worrying.
He's mean as hell.
Ain't he?
He never used to lay a hand on me.
But my mom...
...he wasn't too concerned
with beating her up.
He used to say she could take it.
I tried, you know, I...
...I tried convincing her
to run away with me.
She wouldn't leave him.
This one time...
...he came to pick us up.
We were at the movies, me and my mom.
He had been drinking.
So she got on his case
about it and started yelling.
He lost control...
...and the car crashed.
I watched her die.
And then...
...the cops came...
...but they were his friends.
They made sure nothing bad
would happen to him.
And then after that, I guess...
I guess, I was the only one
around to get angry at.
He'd...
...he'd always feel bad...
...the day after...
...so he'd buy me a present.
A dress, some shoes...
...a puppy.
And every time...
...he promised
he wouldn't lose control again.
But he's a liar.
- Just like me.
- No.
God made a mistake giving you to him.
You're good.
That's something you can trust.
Something else you can trust...
...you ain't never gonna see him again.
Come on.
You're so clean.
I kinda got... got used to
the fact of you smelling bad.
I thought that was you the whole time.
Hey! You're freezing!
- Really?
- Yeah.
- How about this one?
- Yeah. That's even worse.
- Is this better than the tarp?
- Yeah.
Have you ever kissed a girl, Jonas?
Blaise!
What's out there?
I don't see anything.
Blaise, quiet.
I don't know what's wrong with him.
We gotta go. Casey, we gotta go, now.
Go, go, go.
Last time you hopped in the back of
somebody's car without them knowing...
...it got you into some trouble, Mr. Ford.
- Give me your gun.
- Don't carry one.
Slow.
Put your hands on the wheel.
How'd you find us?
Got word of a report
from a pawnshop owner in town.
Said a young boy
tried to sell him an old pistol.
Says the boy was with
a pretty little blonde and a dog too.
That got my attention
even if the rest didn't quite add up.
Motel must've been mighty hard
to resist after a storm like that.
- Havin' fun spendin' our money?
- It ain't your money.
Drive.
You're gonna get that poor girl killed,
you know that, don't you?
- I'm saving her.
- You're chin deep in shit here, son.
The longer you play this out,
the worse off you'll be.
So let's just put the gun down, go get Casey
and the money and be done with all this.
The money's gone.
- We got mugged by a bum in Crow Lake.
- You expect me to believe that?
- Believe what you want, just keep driving.
- What's in your head, boy?
How can you possibly think
you're gonna get away with this?
We just will. We deserve to.
I hate to break the news to you, Mr. Ford...
...but who deserves what
don't mean diddily in the real world.
One thing's for sure, you two sure left
a nice trail of bread crumbs behind ya.
- Slow down.
- Couple runaways with...
...travel packs and a dopey ol' dog...
...that's an image that tends
to linger in people's minds.
I said slow down!
You stole a lot of money, Mr. Ford.
When you steal from a man,
he doesn't stop looking for you.
He doesn't just, one day,
decide to let it go.
- Slow down!
- God forgives, so we don't have to.
Look what you're making an old man do.
You should be ashamed of yourself.
Give me your wallet and phone.
Son, you should get that checked.
You got shit in your ears?
Your hat too.
You think I'm a bad man, Jonas?
I'm the tooth fairy
compared to what's comin'.
I ain't scared of him.
Casey!
- Jonas!
- Casey!
What happened?
- What happened?
- How does it look?
This is bad. You need to go to the hospital.
No, no, no hospital.
They'll be waiting for us.
Here. Just hold it there! Hold it there!
Ma'am, I need some things.
Nothing back here I'm allowed to sell you
without a parent and a prescription, hun.
I need disinfectant and stuff to numb pain.
Someone you know hurting?
Here just... take it.
Just give me what I need. Please.
He's my friend, he...
- ...he's bleeding and it's really bad.
- Then you better get them to a hospital.
- We can't!
- I want to help you...
...I can't just give you what you're asking.
I'm not asking.
Don't.
Jonas, come on, help me out.
I'm sorry!
Okay.
Hold me, hold me. Come on.
Keep pressing!
Okay. Okay.
Open, open, open.
You're gonna need to keep still, okay?
I'm so... Jonas, please, you gotta stop.
You gotta stop moving.
You're doing really good.
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Hey, cowboy.
How you feelin'?
You saved me.
What do you think?
It's no ocean, but it's ours.
We need to rethink a few things.
I know.
We just need to figure out a way to...
...cover a lot of ground quickly.
That'll be tough with Blaise.
- You looking for the gun?
- Yeah.
It's gone.
- What?
- I got rid of it this morning.
- While you were passed out.
- Casey, why would you do that?
Because it scares me.
It scares me more to think about
what we're supposed to do without it.
- That gun keeps us safe and you know it.
- I don't want to be those kind of people.
- What kind of people?
- The kind that sticks a gun...
...in someone's face to get what they want.
I don't want to be those kind
of people either, Casey.
But we have to be realistic about this.
It's only a matter of time before someone
sees us with Blaise and puts it together.
He's gonna get us caught again and when
he does we need to be ready for it.
Casey. Where is it?
I'm not saying.
We need it, Casey.
It's just in case someone
stronger than me tries to hurt you.
No one's stronger than you, Jonas.
Hi there.
Hi, sir.
What can I help you with?
Where'd you go?
- Where's Blaise?
- He's gone!
- I gave him up just like you wanted.
- Hey, Casey!
He was my only friend before you.
And I abandoned him to keep you safe!
Keep me safe?
What are you talking about, Casey?
This has all been to protect you.
- That's the reason for my whole plan!
- What plan?
You didn't have a plan!
You barely gave it a thought!
There wasn't time for that, Casey.
I had to get you out of that house.
Why? Why couldn't you just
leave me right where I was?
You stole the money. You had to leave.
- Not me. Not Blaise!
- So why are you still here then?
Why did you even come?
Because you weren't leaving without me...
...and he was coming after you.
That's why I left. To get you out of there.
To protect you. And I still am.
If my daddy finds us, he'll beat me
two inches from death...
...but you...
...he'll go all the way.
- Let's go get Blaise.
- No.
- Casey, we can make it work...
- It's done!
Let's pack. We're already behind.
You hate me?
No.
I love you.
I love you too.
Just... just wait one sec.
Hello?
Jonas?
Son, is that you?
Pa.
Jonas?
Thank God. Are you alright?
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm alright.
Where are you?
Whatever we've done to...
make you abandon us, I...
You didn't do nothin'.
Casey's dad is after us.
He's dangerous, Pa.
He's a thief and a killer.
The chief too.
Well, come home. You'll be safe here.
Casey won't be.
He'll come after us, take her away and
there won't be anything we can do about it.
Well, then, we'll go to the police
and tell them what you're telling...
They are the police, Pa.
My word won't hold up against theirs.
- Son, listen to me...
- Tell Ma I love her...
...and I'll be home in a little while.
- I sent something in the post for you.
- Jonas, don't you hang up now.
- There's more comin'.
- Jonas!
Sorry, folks.
Looks like we're being pulled over.
Oh, my God, Jonas.
Get the bags ready.
Son, I'm going to need you to keep your seat.
Sir. I'll pay you, okay?
I got a lot of money!
- Listen, sir...
- No, no, don't open the door, please!
Son!
Afternoon, officers!
Well, hey, boy. Sure am glad to see you.
Step off the bus, Mr. Ford.
Hey!
There's my angel.
Everything's fine, folks. Police matter.
Casey.
Casey, let's go.
Well, goddamn, girl.
No. Don't let him take us! No.
Casey. It's time to go home, honey.
That'll be all.
- Where's the rest of it?
- I told the sheriff.
We got mugged in Crow Lake.
That's all that's left.
Casey. The truth.
Right now.
Okay! We buried it!
That's a little vague.
No! Back north.
Just in case we'd wanna come back.
Get your ass up.
Get back in the car!
You did pretty good considering.
You even let my daughter give up the thing
she loves most in the whole world.
'Cause you thought it set you free.
Pretty cold, Mr. Ford.
Funny thing is, abandoning the dog
is what got you caught.
I got a call from a vet in Hodgeville.
Someone brought him in to check his ID.
He had a microchip under his ear.
When you scan it, our info comes up.
We figured the only reason to ditch
the pup is you was aiming to take a bus.
Blaise is our dog, Casey.
Not everything's as simple
as it seems when you're a kid.
It's a mean world and the angels
left us to fend for ourselves.
You gotta fight for what's yours,
however you know how.
You wouldn't know an angel
if you were beatin' on one.
That's what you do, ain't it?
You beat on angels?
How we on gas?
- Not in the red yet.
- Take the next stop anyway.
These kids are probably hungry.
Why don't you let me take over?
These patties take two hands to eat.
If you insist.
What's happening?
- Jonas.
- He's alright.
A couple of crushed valium
never hurt anybody.
What the hell you doing?
This is as far as I go.
I'm taking my half of the money.
Your half, wherever it is, is your problem.
Your fault. I'm done with this nonsense.
You fuck.
Sweet dreams, darlin'.
That's the least you deserve.
You really fucked me on this one, Wayne.
Goddammit! Fuck!
How much further, Casey?
Casey.
Fifty miles. Maybe less.
Up ahead, through that clearing.
I'd be sure if I were you.
Come on, boy. Yeah! Come on! There ya go!
Casey.
Casey, what are you doing?
Casey, please.
Casey, please!
- Come on, baby girl. Let's get this done.
- Casey, please don't. Casey.
Casey! Casey!
Casey!
All you had to do was mind your own business.
Let's go.
Casey!
- It's under here somewhere.
- What are you waiting for then?
I'll try that way.
No use stalling.
Hey.
- Baby girl.
- I'll kill you before I let you kill him.
Nobody's killin' anybody.
Put the gun down, Casey, and we'll talk...
You shut up!
Casey, you're scaring me.
Okay, I admit it. I know I've failed you.
I lost my heart, I lost my way.
But I swear on my soul,
on your mama's grave I'll let him go.
I don't believe you.
You know what happens if you
pull that trigger, don't you?
You'll be alone.
I know you're with Jonas now.
Pretty soon he's gonna get tired
and he's gonna wanna go home.
You'll see, one day he'll quit
on you quick as light.
It's coming, I guarantee it.
Casey, you're my angel.
Baby girl, please.
It's you and me, right?
- Say it.
- Shut up.
It's you and...
I'm sorry.